Arun BS

Senior Software Engineer

Personal Info

Address

531, 3rd 'A' Main, 8h Cross, Ayyappa Temple Street, Venkatapura,

Koramangala,

Bangalore - 560034

Phone

9739185574

E-mail

bsarunmca@gmail.com

Date of birth

1989-10-30

Skills

React JS

Redux

JavaScript, ES6

jQuery

NodeJS

Webpack

Python

Angular JS (1.x)

AJAX, JSON

HTML, HTML5

CSS, CSS3, SCSS

Bootstrap

Lesshint, JSInspect

Creative front end developer with 6+ years of work experience in developing the web application and embedded application as per W3 Standards. Onsite experience(Japan) to discuss about the architecture and planning for the upcoming projects of MFP and supporting MSM and TSIP. Team player with good listening skills and innovative ideas to make attractive designs and development. Good exposure to AGILE and SCRUM methodologies.

Experience

2017-11 - Senior Software Engineer

present Toshiba Software India Private Limted

WebPanel

Environment: ReactJS, Redux, ESLint, Python, HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, JavaScript **Description**: Toshiba Webpanel, Toshiba Printer has embedded browser for MFP (Multi Functional printers). My role and responsibility is to develop UI for MFP. Traveled Japan(Onsite) to discuss about the architecture and planning for the upcoming modules and providing support for offsite members and establish communication bridge between

Toshiba MSM and Toshiba TSIP.

WPSG - WebPanel Style Guide

Environment: ReactJS, HTML5, CSS3.

Description: WPSG is a toolkit for developing the WebPanel UI.

2015-12 - **Software Engineer**

2017-11 Payoda Technologies

Arista CVP

Environment: HTML5, CSS3, Angularjs, jQuery, d3js, Requirejs, AJAX, JSON, NPM,

Grunt, ESLint, Lesshint, JSInspect, Jasmine.

Description: CLOUDVISION is a central portal for managing all the network switches making it easier to configure and monitor better than ever. CVP combines a front-end web-based dashboard for performing the pre-integrated operational workflows and a backend state repository and analytics engine for maintaining historic network state.

2014-07 - Frontend Developer

2015-11 Sakhatech Information Systems Pvt. Ltd

Tellofy

Environment: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 3.0, JQuery, AJAX, JSON, Facebook API,

Google plus API, Twiter API, & Linkedin API

Description: Tellofy is an online reputation management tool. It provide businesses with real-time review and feedback. It enables businesses to gather feedback, analyze consumer sentiments, showcase positive reviews and address solvable grievances.

TNT

Environment: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 3.0, JQuery, AJAX, JSON

Description: Web applications for shipping company.

TNT - Customer, TNT - Customer Care, TNT - PUD(Purchase and delivery details)

Education

Erode Arts and Science College

2013 • MCA - Master of Computer Application

Jairam Arts & Science College

• BSc - Maths with Computer Application